Edward C. Blomeyer photographic collection, Inclusive: 1906-1923, Bulk: 1912-1920
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
- Vacation, 1912-1920; 3
  - Yellowstone National Park, Wyoming, 1912-1920; 5
    This group of photographs includes scenes of Yellowstone National park including geyser basins, water falls, gorges, and buffalo.
    - Yellowstone National Park, Wyoming, 1912-1920 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Yellowstone National Park, Wyoming, 1912-1920 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Yellowstone National Park, Wyoming, 1912-1920 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Yellowstone National Park, Wyoming, 1912-1920 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Niagra Falls, 1912-1920; 6
    The Blomeyer family traveled to Niagra Falls, circa 1920. This subseries shows scenes including Honeymoon Bridge, and an early version of the "Maid of the Mist" that still transports passengers close to the falls.
    Edward, Earle, Mary, and Amma Blomeyer pose with the British flag, Niagra Falls, Ontario, Canada. The digital image is from a scan of a 6 by 3 ¾ inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-vacat-893.1.tif. Photo taken by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1920.
    The Honeymoon Bridge connected both sides of Niagra Falls: New York and Ontario, Canada. The digital image is from a scan of a 6 by 3 ¾ inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-vacat-790.3.tif. Photo taken by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1920.
    The "Maid of the Mist" transported visitors to the falls. The digital image is from a scan of a 6 by 3 ¾ inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-vacat-773.2.tif. Photo taken by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1920.
    - Vacation: Niagra Falls, 1912-1920 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Vacation: Niagra Falls, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 3:41)
    - Vacation: Niagra Falls 773-1: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-vacat-773.1.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 3:42)
    - Vacation: Niagra Falls: “Maid of the Mist” Under the Falls, Blomeyer Boys Looks On, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 3:43)
    - Vacation: Niagra Falls 893-1: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-vacat-893.1.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 3:44)
    - Vacation: Niagra Falls 773-2: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-vacat-773.2.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 3:45)
    - Vacation: Niagara Falls: “Honeymoon Bridge” 790-3: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-vacat-790.3.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 3:46)
  - General, 1900s-1920s; 7
    This group of photographs includes lake scenes, rivers, ponds, creeks, mountains, and wooded areas or forests. It also contains images of bridges, monuments, fountains, and structures including buildings, and cabins. A few images contain a group of Native Americans.
    Native Americans are photographed in an unknown location. The digital image is from a scan of a 6 by 3 ¾ inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-vacat-790.1.tif. Photo taken by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1920.
    Native Americans and a group are photographed canoeing in an unknown location. The digital image is from a scan of a 6 by 3 ¾ inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-vacat-790.2.tif. Photo taken by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1920.
    - Vacation: General: Unidentified Locations (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Vacation: General: Unidentified Locations (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Vacation: General: Unidentified Locations (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Vacation: General: Unidentified Locations (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Vacation: General: Native Americans in Ceremony 790-1: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-vacat-790.1.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 3:47)
    - Vacation: General: Native Americans in Canoe 790-2: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-vacat-790.2.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 3:48)
    - Vacation: General: Native Americans in Canoe, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 3:49)
    - Vacation: General: Native Americans and People in Wooded Area, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 3:50)
    - Vacation: General: Lighthouse and Waterway 951-4: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-vacat-951.4.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 3:51)
    - Vacation: General: Unidentified Abandoned Structure, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 3:52)
    - Vacation: General: Unidentified Building, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 3:53)
    - Vacation: General: Building: “Comfort Station” Unknown Location, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 3:54)
    - Vacation: General: Building: “Comfort Station” Unknown Location, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 3:55)
    - Vacation: General: Building: “Comfort Station” Unknown Location, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 3:56)
    - Vacation: General: Unidentified Building with Lily Pond 951-2: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-vacat-951.2.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 3:57)
    - Vacation: General: Scenic Pond with Swans-Unknown Location 951-1: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-vacat-951.1.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 3:58)
    - Vacation: General: Monument of Stag-Unknown Location 951-3: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-vacat-951.3.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 3:59)
    - Vacation: General: Scenic Duck Pond-Unknown Location, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 3:60)
    - Vacation: General: View from Mountain-Unknown Location, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 3:61)
    - Vacation: General: Scenic Landscape View-Unknown Location, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 3:62)
    - Vacation: General: Outdoor Dining Area-Unknown Location, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 3:63)
    - Vacation: General: Scenic Landscape View-Unknown Location, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 3:64)
    - Vacation: General: Fountain and Park Area-Unidentified Location 804-3: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-vacat-804.3.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 3:65)
    - Vacation: General: Fountain and Park Area-Unidentified Location, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 3:66)
    - Vacation: General: Pile of “Buffalo Bones”, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 3:67)
    - Vacation: General: Unidentified Location: Bridge, Mountain, and Lake, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 3:68)
    - Vacation: General: Unidentified River, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 3:69)
    - Vacation: General: Unidentified River, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 3:70)
    - Vacation: General: Unidentified Creek, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 3:71)
    - Vacation: General: Unidentified Location: Lake Scene, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 3:72)
    - Vacation: General: Unidentified Location: Lake Scene, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 3:73)
    - Vacation: General: Unidentified Location: Lake Scene, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 3:74)
    - Vacation: General: Unidentified Location: Lake Scene, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 3:75)
    - Vacation: General: Unidentified Location: Lake Scene, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 3:76)
    - Vacation: General: Unidentified Location: Lake Scene, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 3:77)
    - Vacation: General: Unidentified Location: Lake Scene, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 3:78)
    - Vacation: General: Unidentified Location: Lake Scene, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 3:79)
    - Vacation: General: Unidentified Location: Lake Scene, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 3:80)
    - Vacation: General: Unidentified Location: Lake Scene, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 3:81)
    - Vacation: General: Unidentified Location: Lake Scene, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 3:82)
    - Vacation: General: Unidentified Location: Lake Scene, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 3:83)
    - Vacation: General: Unidentified Location: Lake Scene, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 3:84)
    - Vacation: General: Unidentified Location: Lake Scene, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 3:85)
    - Vacation: General: Unidentified Location: Lake Scene, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 3:86)
    - Vacation: General: Unidentified Location: Cabin in Woods, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 3:87)
    - Vacation: General: Unidentified Location: Mountain Scene, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 3:88)
    - Vacation: General: Unidentified Location: Wooded Area, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 3:89)
    - Vacation: General: Unidentified Location: Wooded Area, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 3:90)
    - Vacation: General: Unidentified Location: Wooded Area, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 3:91)
    - Vacation: General: Unidentified Location: Wooded Area, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 3:92)
    - Vacation: General: Unidentified Location: Wooded Area, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 3:93)
    - Vacation: General: Unidentified Location: Wooded Area, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 3:94)
    - Vacation: General: Unidentified Location: Wooded Area, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 3:95)
    - Vacation: General: Unidentified Location: Wooded Area, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 3:96)
    - Vacation: General: Unidentified Location: Wooded Roadway, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 3:97)
    - Vacation: General: Unidentified Location: Wooded Roadway, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 3:98)
    - Vacation: General: Unidentified Location: Stone Cylindrical Monuments, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 3:99)
    - Vacation: General: Unidentified Location: Unidentified Monument, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 3:100)
    - Vacation: General: Unidentified Location: Bethesda, Maryland: Monument, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 3:101)
    - Vacation: General: Unidentified Location: Coastal Scene, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 3:102)
    - Vacation: General: Unidentified Location: Coastal Scene, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 3:103)
    - Vacation: General: Unidentified Location: Coastal Scene, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 3:104)
    - Vacation: General: Unidentified Location: Gravesite, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 3:105)
- People, circa 1900s-1920s; 4
  The majority of the people in this series are unidentified with the exception of a few including E.C. Blomeyer and his immediate family. Most of the locations include Missouri, Texas, and a few images taken after the Blowmeyer's move to Illinois after 1920.
  - E.C. Blomeyer and Family, circa 1900s-1920s; 1
    This subseries includes images of Edward Charles (E.C.) Blomeyer and his immediate family: wife Amma, daughter Mary, and sons Edward and Earle. Included are candid photos taken in Missouri, Waco, Texas, and Illinois.
    Amma Blomeyer with daughter, Mary, stand along the banks of the Brazos River, Waco, Texas. The digital image is from a scan of a 6 by 3 ¾ inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-cprb-816.9.tif. Photo by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1914.
    Edward Charles Blowmeyer prepares his camera on one of Cameron Park's bluffs, Waco, Texas, circa 1917. Scanned from a photo print. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-pplblofmly-001.tif.
    Pictured near Chicago, Illinois, in 1923, are E.C. Blomeyer, far left, sons Edward and Earle, and an unidentified man. The digital image is from a scan of a 6 by 3 ¾ inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-pplblofmly-798.1.tif.
    Edward and Earle Blomeyer stand with their father's Ford Model-T. The digital image is from a scan of a 6 by 3 ¾ inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-transp-897.1.tif. Photo taken by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1918.
    - People: E.C. Blomeyer and Family, 1912-1920 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - People: E.C. Blomeyer and Family, 1912-1920 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - People: E.C. Blomeyer and Family, 1912-1920 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - People: E.C. Blomeyer and Family, 1912-1920 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - People: Amma Blomeyer Posing on Cameron Park Bluffs 885-1: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-pplblofmly-885.1.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 4:1)
    - People: Amma and E.C. Blomeyer Sitting 891-1: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-pplblofmly-891.1.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 4:2)
    - People: Amma Blomeyer and Children 795-2: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-pplblofmly-795.2.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 4:3)
    - People: Amma, Mary, Edward, and Earle, at Roadside, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 4:4)
    - People: Amma Blomeyer Sitting in Wooded Area, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 4:5)
    - People: E.C. Blomeyer’s son on Baylor University’s Carroll Field (1), 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 4:6)
    - People: E.C. Blomeyer’s son on Baylor University’s Carroll Field (2), 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 4:7)
    - People: E.C. Blomeyer’s son on Baylor University’s Carroll Field (3), 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 4:8)
    - People: E.C. Blomeyer and Friend, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 4:9)
    - People: E.C. Blomeyer and Family Sons: Edward and Earle. Mother Amma Blomeyer, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 4:10)
    - People: E.C. Blomeyer, with Camera, looking down from Cameron Park bluff onto river 507-2: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-pplblofmly-507.2.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 4:11)
    - People: E.C. Blomeyer Family Home 789-3: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-pplblofmly-789.3.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 4:12)
    - People: E.C. Blomeyer Children (1) 776-3: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-pplblofmly-776.3.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 4:13)
    - People: E.C. Blomeyer Children (2) 770-1: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-pplblofmly-770.1.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 4:14)
    - People: E.C. Blomeyer with Sons and Friends 798-1: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-pplblofmly-798.1.tif, 1923 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 4:15)
    - People: E.C. Blomeyer and Family, Sons: Edward and Earle, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 4:16)
    - People: Edward or Earle Blomeyer in Garden at Residence, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 4:17)
    - People: Edward and Earle Blomeyer in Canoe on Lake, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 4:18)
    - People: Edward or Earle Blomeyer at Bird Bath at Residence, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 4:19)
    - People: Mary Blomeyer at Bird Bath at Residence, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 4:20)
    - People: Edward and Earle Blomeyer, and Friend, Throwing Stones in Lake, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 4:21)
    - People: Amma Blomeyer, 1912-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 4:22)
    - People: E.C. Blomeyer and Family Sons: Edward and Earle, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 4:23)
    - People: Mary Blomeyer-Playing Guitar, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 4:24)
    - People: Amma Blomeyer and Sons, Edward and Earle, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 4:25)
    - People: Mary Blomeyer and Group, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 4:26)
    - People: Amma Blomeyer with Family Group, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 4:27)
    - People: Amma Blomeyer with Family Group, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 4:28)
    - People: Mary Blomeyer, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 4:29)
    - People: Mary Blomeyer, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 4:30)
    - People: Mary Blomeyer, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 4:31)
    - People: Mary Blomeyer, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 4:32)
    - People: Edward and Earle Blomeyer, 1912-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 4:33)
    - People: Edward and Earle Blomeyer, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 4:34)
    - People: Mary Blomeyer, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 4:35)
    - People: Edward and Earle Blomeyer at Edge of a Lake, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 4:36)
    - People: Edward or Earle Blomeyer, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 4:37)
    - People: Amma Blomeyer, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 4:38)
    - People: Edward and Earle Blomeyer, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 4:39)
    - People: Edward and Earle Blomeyer, 1912-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 4:40)
    - People: Amma Blomeyer with Sons, Edward and Earle, in Garden, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 4:41)
    - People: Edward or Earle Blomeyer in Front of Car: Digital ID:, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 4:42)
    - People: E.C. Blomeyer Carrying Edward or Earle in Water at Coast, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 4:43)
    - People: Amma Blomeyer with sons, Edward and Earle, at Indian Springs Park, Waco, TX., 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 4:44)
  - General, 1900s-1920s; 2; The 37 Photo negative folders included in this sub-series contain 128 negatives.
    The items in this subseries include pictures of unidentified people with the exception of a few. Locations include Missouri, Texas, Illinois, and other unidentified locations, some were possibly taken while on vacation.
    - People: General, 1912-1920 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - People: General, 1912-1920 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - People: General, 1912-1920 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - People: General, 1912-1920 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - People: General, 1912-1920 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - People: General, 1912-1920 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - People: General, 1912-1920 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - People: General: Unidentified, 1912-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 4:45)
    - People: General: Unidentified, 1912-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 4:46)
    - People: General: Unidentified x 5, 1912-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 4:47)
    - People: General: Unidentified x 6, 1912-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 4:48)
    - People: General: Horseback Riding, 1912-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 4:49)
    - People: General: Unidentified x 5, 1912-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 4:50)
    - People: General: “The Proposal”, 1912-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 4:51)
    - People: General: Unidentified x 8, 1912-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 4:52)
    - People: General: Unidentified x 6, 1912-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 4:53)
    - People: General: Unidentified: Woman with Cat, 1912-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 4:54)
    - People: General: Unidentified x 5, 1912-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 4:55)
    - People: General: Unidentified x 4, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 4:56)
    - People: General: Unidentified x 4, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 4:57)
    - People: General: Unidentified x 4, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 4:58)
    - People: General: Unidentified x 4, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 4:59)
    - People: General: Unidentified x 4, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 4:60)
    - People: General: Unidentified x 5, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 4:61)
    - People: General: Unidentified x 7, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 4:62)
    - People: General: Unidentified x 3, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 4:63)
    - People: General: Unidentified x 6, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 4:64)
    - People: General: Unidentified x 3, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 4:65)
    - People: General: Unidentified x 2, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 4:66)
    - People: General: Unidentified x 4, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 4:67)
    - People: General: People Swimming 896-2: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-pplgen-896.2.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 4:68)
    - People: General: Unidentified x 3, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 4:69)
    - People: General: Unidentified x 4, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 4:70)
    - People: General: Unidentified x 5, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 4:71)
    - People: General: Unidentified x 3, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 4:72)
    - People: General: Unidentified x 4, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 4:73)
    - People: General: Unidentified x 4, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 4:74)
    - People: General: Unidentified x 5, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 4:75)
    - People: General: Unidentified x 4, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 4:76)
    - People: General: Unidentified x 4, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 4:77)
    - People: Blomeyer Family Housekeeper x 3, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 4:78)
    - People: General: Unidentified, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 4:79)
    - People: General: Ellen Boyce x 3, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 4:80)
    - People: General: Ellen Boyce x 3, 1912-1920 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 4:81)
- Missouri, 1906-1912; 5
  The photos in the series include the aftermath of a flood and subsequent damage. Other images show general street scenes in rural areas and towns. Another group of photos is of the John Robinson Circus in an unknown town. Shown is its arrival by train followed by a circus parade. Other images show lakes, rivers, and railroad tracks.
  Circus train: The John Robinson Circus comes to an unidentified Missouri town by rail. The digital image is from a scan of a 4 by 3 ¼- inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-missouri-755.3.tif. Photo taken by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1910.
  Flood Scene: A neighboring flooded field poses a potential threat to the property seen in this picture. The digital image is from a scan of a 4 by 3 ¼- inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-missouri-910.3.tif. Photo taken by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1910.
  Attendees are seen entering the John Robinson Circus. The digital image is from a scan of a 4 by 3 ¼- inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-missouri-784.4.tif. Photo taken by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1910.
  Circus Parade: Performers of the John Robinson Circus take part in a parade in a Missouri town. The digital image is from a scan of a 4 by 3 ¼- inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-missouri-755.2.tif. Photo taken by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1910.
  Circus Parade: Elephants of the John Robinson Circus march down the street of a Missouri town. The digital image is from a scan of a 4 by 3 ¼- inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-missouri-754.3.tif. Photo taken by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1910.
  Circus Parade: A John Robinson Circus parade. The digital image is from a scan of a 4 by 3 ¼- inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-missouri-755.4.tif. Photo taken by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1910.
  Flood Scene: This image shows a group of people navigating on a flooded river. The digital image is from a scan of a 4 by 3 ¼- inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-missouri-793.1.tif. Photo taken by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1910.
  Circus Parade: Camels of the John Robinson Circus march down the street of a Missouri town. The digital image is from a scan of a 4 by 3 ¼- inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-missouri-754.4.tif. Photo taken by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1910.
  In this unidentified industrial facility, the large belt driven fly-wheel was used as a power source for machinery or equipment of equal proportions. The digital image is from a scan of a 4 by 3 ¼- inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-missouri-753.2.tif. Photo taken by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1906
  - Missouri: Flood Damage Aftermath 793-1: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-missouri-793.1.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 5:1)
  - Missouri: Flood Damage Aftermath, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 5:2)
  - Missouri: Flood Damage Aftermath, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 5:3)
  - Missouri: Flood Damage Aftermath, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 5:4)
  - Missouri: Flood Damage Aftermath, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 5:5)
  - Missouri: Flood Damage Aftermath, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 5:6)
  - Missouri: Flood Damage Aftermath, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 5:7)
  - Missouri: Flood Damage Aftermath, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 5:8)
  - Missouri: Flood Damage Aftermath, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 5:9)
  - Missouri: Flood Damage Aftermath, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 5:10)
  - Missouri: Flood Damage Aftermath, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 5:11)
  - Missouri: Flood Damage Aftermath, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 5:12)
  - Missouri: Flood Damage Aftermath, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 5:13)
  - Missouri: Flood Damage Aftermath, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 5:14)
  - Missouri: Flood Damage Aftermath 792-3: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-missouri-792.3.tif, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 5:15)
  - Missouri: Flood Damage Aftermath, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 5:16)
  - Missouri: Flood Damage Aftermath 910-2:, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 5:17)
  - Missouri: Flood Damage Aftermath 910-3:, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 5:18)
  - Missouri: Flood Damage Aftermath, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 5:19)
  - Missouri: Flood Damage Aftermath, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 5:20)
  - Missouri: Flood Damage Aftermath, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 5:21)
  - Missouri: Flood Damage Aftermath, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 5:22)
  - Missouri: Flood Damage Aftermath, 1906-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 5:23)